Next, let's go ahead and build the component for both of our submit buttons down here.
接着我们将为底部的提交按钮构建组件
So what we can do is, first,
首先
let's go ahead and add a method to our AddEntry component,
向 AddEntry 组件添加一个方法
and we will call it submit.
称其为 submit
And what this is going to do is,
首先
first, it needs to grab the key for this specific day.
它将获取这一天的键
And if you remember, inside of helpers,
在 helpers 中
we have this function right here.
有一个这样的函数
Basically, what it's going to do,
它将返回一个
is it's going to return a date after it has formatted it,
设定格式的日期
and we will use this formatted date for the key for the specific date.
我们将使用这个具有格式的日期作为特定日期的键
The reason we're doing this is because
这么做的原因是
the calendar component that we're going to be using
我们将使用的 calendar 组件
needs the dates formatted this way, so we'll just go with it.
需要这种格式的日期 因此将这么设定
So what we'll do first is,
我们首先将
let's go ahead and import that timeToString method that we just talked about.
导入刚刚提到的 timeToString 方法
And then inside of submit,
然后在 submit 中
what we're going to do is,
我们将
let's create a key variable,
创建一个 key 变量
which is just going to be whatever is returned from invoking timeToString.
它将为调用 timeToString 后返回的内容
Let's create an entry which is just going to be the start state.
我们创建一个 entry 它将是一个起始状态
So it's going to grab everything from the state which are all of our metrics up here.
并从 state 中获取所有内容 也就是这里的指标
Then there's a few different things we want to do in this function.
然后我们将在此函数中进行几项设置
Not all of them we will do right now,
但是现在不会进行所有设置
so I'll just create a note for ourselves.
所以添加一些注释
We want to eventually, we'll update Redux.
我们想要最终更新下 Redux
We also want to navigate to home when we add in navigation.
我们还想在添加导航功能后导航到主屏幕上
We want to save this information to our database, and then eventually,
我们想要将这些信息保存到数据库中
we are going to want to clear the local notifications so
我们将清空本地通知
the user doesn't get a notification to submit their information for this day.
使用户不会收到关于提交当天信息的通知
But right now, what we can do is we want to go ahead and reset our states,
但是现在我们能做的是重置状态
and we will just reset all of these back to zero.
将所有这一切重置为 0
So I'm actually just going to go ahead and copy this and paste it right there.
直接复制这些代码并粘贴到这里
And so now, whenever we run submit,
现在 每当我们运行 submit 时
right now, basically, what's going to happen is,
所发生的情况是
we grab the key which we're not using yet,
获取 key 暂时不会用到该 key
we also grab all these states which we're again not using,
我们还将获取所有这些状态 暂时也不会用到
and then we just reset our local state.
然后重置本地状态
So now, what I want to do is,
现在
let's go ahead and up here,
转到这里
create our submit button.
创建提交按钮
This is going to take in an onPress method.
传入 onPress 方法
And then what we're going to do is,
该按钮的 UI 将是
the UI for this is going to be a touchable component.
可触摸组件
There's a few different ones you can use.
你可以使用几种不同的组件
I like using TouchableOpacity,
我喜欢使用 TouchableOpacity
and then we'll also grab text.
然后获取 Text
So we will say TouchableOpacity,
输入 TouchableOpacity
and when this component is pressed,
当该组件被点击时
notice it's not onClick because we are in React Native,
注意不是 onClick 因为我们位于 React Native 中
so that might be something that takes a little bit of time to get used to.
可能需要一段时间才能适应这种区别
We will say, whenever this component is pressed,
每当该组件被点击时
run the onPress function that we're passing in.
运行传入的 onPress 函数
And then for now, the text,
设定文本
let's just say submit, and then now,
输入 SUBMIT
what we can do is down here inside of
然后滚动到下面
our render method below this object that key section right here,
在渲染方法中的 key 对象下面
let's go ahead and render our submit button.
渲染我们的提交按钮
What we're going to pass it is our submit method that we created right here.
传入在这里创建的 submit 方法
So just to test this out,
测试下
let's go ahead and change bike to 10.
将 bike 改为 10
We'll change eat to five,
将 eat 改为 5
and then inside of our render method,
在 render 方法中
let's just go ahead and render, let's say,
渲染 JSON.stringify
JSON.stringify sjo we can see the states.
以便看到状态
And then now, if everything's working correctly, it looks like it is.
现在如果一切正常的话 看起来正常
So here's our state. When we hit submit, what should happen?
这是我们的状态 点击提交 会发生什么？
And just notice, it gets reset to zeros.
重置为 0 了
So before we move on,
在继续之前
let me go ahead and delete this stuff,
删掉这行内容
and then we will change our states back to what it should be which is just all zeros.
并将状态改成应该处于的状态 也就是全为 0